https://www.cera-india.com/privacypolicy/

Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with www.cera-india.com. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests.
Sharing of personal information
The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us or shared by us with our corporate affiliates, dealers, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small piece of information stored on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. www.cera-india.com places temporary cookies in your computer’s hard drive. www.cera-india.com’s cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.
Security
Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. Sensitive data is hashed or encrypted when it is stored in our infrastructure. Sensitive data is decrypted, processed and immediately re-encrypted or discarded when no longer necessary. We host web services in audited data centers, with restricted access to the data processing servers. Controlled access, recorded and live-monitored video feeds, 24/7 staffed security and biometrics provided in such data centers ensure that we provide secure hosting.
Opt-Out Policy
Please email ecom@cera-india.com if you no longer wish to receive any information from us.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.
Questions?
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: ecom@cera-india.com
Download Mobile App
Awards & Accolades
Blog
Certifications
Media Coverage
Video
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Catalogue
Warrarnty Manual
Newsletter
Career
Site Map
Glossary
© 2019 CERA Sanitaryware Limited. All rights reserved.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
